<addon id="skin.aura" name="Aura" provider-name="jurialmunkey" version="1.0.5">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.15.0" />
        <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.4.0" />
        <import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="0.0.5" />
        <import addon="plugin.program.autocompletion" version="1.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.studios.white" version="0.0.10" />
        <import addon="resource.images.moviegenreicons.transparent" version="0.0.6" />
    </requires>
    <extension debugging="false" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1" point="xbmc.gui.skin">
        <res aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" height="1080" width="1920" />
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Minimalistic. Customisable. Multiple Widgets.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Minimalista. Personzalizable. M√∫ltiples Widgets.</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Min. Customisable. Multiple Widgets.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Minimaliste. Personnalisable. Widgets Multiple.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Aura is highly customisable skin with multiple widgets and a horizontal home menu. Aura combines the minimalism and rounded edges of Arctic Zephyr with the sleek customisability of Horizon. Whilst the best Aura experience is had with a remote, Aura has been designed to accomodate mouse and touch users where possible.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Aura es un skin altamente personalizable con m√∫ltiples widgets y un men√∫ de inicio horizontal. Aura combina el minimalismo y los bordes redondeados de Arctic Zephyr con la personalizaci√≥n elegante de Horizon. Mientras que la mejor experiencia de Aura es teniendo un control remoto, Aura se ha dise√±ado para complacer a los usuarios de mouse y los usuarios del modo t√°ctil siempre que sea posible.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Aura ist ein sehr anpassbarer Skin mit mehreren Widgets und einem horizontalen Home-Men¸. Aura kombiniert den Minimalismus und die abgerundeten Kanten von Arctic Zephyr mit der eleganten Anpassungsf‰higkeit von Horizon. W‰hrend das beste Aura-Erlebnis mit einer Fernbedienung geboten wird, wurde Aura so konzipiert, dass es auch Maus- und Touch-Benutzern nach Mˆglichkeit entgegenkommt.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">Aura est un th√®me hautement personnalisable avec plusieurs widgets et un menu d'accueil horizontal. Aura combine le minimalisme et les bords arrondis de l'Arctic Zephyr avec l'√©l√©gante personnalisation d'Horizon. Alors que la meilleure exp√©rience Aura est acquise avec une t√©l√©commande, Aura a √©t√© con√ßue pour accueillir les utilisateurs de souris et de tactiles dans la mesure du possible.</description>
	<platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share-Alike 4.0</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=328558</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/jurialmunkey/skin.aura</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
